<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Fly-Out</title>
    <link>https://fly-out.fr/public/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Fly-Out</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fly-out.fr/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eureka An old Fashion Equation Solver</title>
      <link>https://fly-out.fr/public/eureka/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 16:22:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fly-out.fr/public/eureka/</guid>
      <description>Eureka An old Fashion Equation Solver During my studies (several years ago), I discovered the Equation solver TkSolver. Some days ago, I was trying to find a GNU equivalent to TkSolver as I wanted to perform some computations. My searches were unsuccessful (not exactly but I didn’t find a similar tool) but I found Eureka Solver which is an old solver (may be the first of this type).
Eureka Solver (and TK solver) is build on the declarative programming approach while the « standard » solvers use a procedural approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Pilot Weather</title>
      <link>https://fly-out.fr/public/posts/japan-pilot-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 16:22:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fly-out.fr/public/posts/japan-pilot-weather/</guid>
      <description>Central Japan Weather briefing The Japan Weather Agency (JMA) provides several charts, forecasts and documents for the aeronautical operations. Navigation inside all the documents could be difficult when you don&amp;rsquo;t know all the expressions, words and abbreviations used. Aim of the page is to present the documents, not to recall the traditional abbreviations used inside METARs, TAFs&amp;hellip;
You should be able to find the charts on this page: link: http://www.data.jma.go.jp/airinfo/index.html[jma website]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Fly-out</title>
      <link>https://fly-out.fr/public/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fly-out.fr/public/about/</guid>
      <description>Fly-out speaks about general aviation, softwares and all that could be part of a technical conversation. The main motivation for writing this website was to share knowledges and tools for pilots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://fly-out.fr/public/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fly-out.fr/public/search/</guid>
      <description>Manticore Search </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>