<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Fly-Out</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Fly-Out</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nagodede.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A-propos de l'auteur</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/pages/whoiam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:28:58 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/pages/whoiam/</guid><description>Sorry, work in progress. Nethertheless, the french page is available.</description></item><item><title>AIP Japan</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/aip/japan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:28:58 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/aip/japan/</guid><description>The list is retrieved from the AIS Japan loadAirportsData ("https:\/\/nagodede.github.io\/aip\/japan\/documents\/info.json"); Effective Date: Process Date: RJAA charts full RJAF charts full RJAH charts full RJAK N/A full RJAM N/A full RJAN charts full RJAW charts full RJAZ charts full RJBB charts full RJBD charts full RJBE charts full RJBK charts full RJBT charts full RJCA N/A full RJCB charts full RJCC charts full RJCH charts full RJCJ charts full RJCK charts full RJCM charts full RJCN charts full RJCO charts full RJCR charts full RJCT charts full RJCW charts full RJDA charts full RJDB charts full RJDC charts full RJDK charts full RJDM N/A full RJDO charts full RJDT charts full RJDU charts full RJEB charts full RJEC charts full RJEO charts full RJER charts full RJFA charts full RJFC charts full RJFE charts full RJFF charts full RJFG charts full RJFK charts full RJFM charts full RJFN charts full RJFO charts full RJFR charts full RJFS charts full RJFT charts full RJFU charts full RJFY charts full RJFZ charts full RJGG charts full RJKA charts full RJKB charts full RJKI charts full RJKN charts full RJNA charts full RJNF charts full RJNG charts full RJNH charts full RJNK charts full RJNO charts full RJNS charts full RJNT charts full RJNW charts full RJNY charts full RJOA charts full RJOB charts full RJOC charts full RJOE charts full RJOF charts full RJOH charts full RJOI charts full RJOK charts full RJOM charts full RJOO charts full RJOR charts full RJOS charts full RJOT charts full RJOW charts full RJOY charts full RJOZ charts full RJSA charts full RJSC charts full RJSD charts full RJSF charts full RJSH charts full RJSI charts full RJSK charts full RJSM charts full RJSN charts full RJSO charts full RJSR charts full RJSS charts full RJST charts full RJSU N/A full RJSY charts full RJTA charts full RJTC charts full RJTE charts full RJTF charts full RJTH charts full RJTJ charts full RJTK charts full RJTL charts full RJTO charts full RJTQ charts full RJTT charts full RJTU charts full RJTY charts full ROAH charts full RODN charts full ROIG charts full ROKJ charts full ROKR charts full ROMD charts full ROMY charts full RORA charts full RORE charts full RORH charts full RORK charts full RORS charts full RORT charts full RORY charts full ROTM charts full ROYN charts full</description></item><item><title>Eureka An old Fashion Equation Solver</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/eureka/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 16:22:49 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/eureka/</guid><description>Eureka An old Fashion Equation Solver During my studies (several years ago), I discovered the Equation solver TkSolver. Some days ago, I was trying to find a GNU equivalent to TkSolver as I wanted to perform some computations. My searches were unsuccessful (not exactly but I didn’t find a similar tool) but I found Eureka Solver which is an old solver (may be the first of this type).
Eureka Solver (and TK solver) is build on the declarative programming approach while the « standard » solvers use a procedural approach.</description></item><item><title>Japan Pilot Weather</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/posts/japan-pilot-weather/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 16:22:49 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/posts/japan-pilot-weather/</guid><description>Central Japan Weather briefing The Japan Weather Agency (JMA) provides several charts, forecasts and documents for the aeronautical operations. Navigation inside all the documents could be difficult when you don&amp;rsquo;t know all the expressions, words and abbreviations used. Aim of the page is to present the documents, not to recall the traditional abbreviations used inside METARs, TAFs&amp;hellip;
You should be able to find the charts on this page: link: http://www.data.jma.go.jp/airinfo/index.html[jma website]</description></item><item><title>About Fly-out</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:28:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/about/</guid><description>Fly-out speaks about general aviation, softwares and all that could be part of a technical conversation. The main motivation for writing this website was to share knowledges and tools for pilots.</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/search/</guid><description>Manticore Search</description></item></channel></rss>