<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aerodynamic on Fly-Out</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/tags/aerodynamic/</link><description>Recent content in Aerodynamic on Fly-Out</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:08:05 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nagodede.github.io/tags/aerodynamic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Propeller Design Documents</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/propeller/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:08:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/propeller/</guid><description>This post tries to list and present relevant documents to design a propeller.
Optimal design and experiment of propellers for high altitude airship
https://doi.org/10.1177/0954410017704217 High altitude propeller design and analysis Using blade element momentum methods with gradient-based design optimmization htpps://doi.org/10.1007/s00158-021-02883-6 Design and Performance Calculation of a Propeller for Very High Altitude Flight High Altitude Propeller Design and Analysis Overview Aerodynamic Design of a Propeller fo High-Altitude Ballon Trajectory Control</description></item><item><title>Free Software for Aeronautics</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/aerosoft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 18:08:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/aerosoft/</guid><description>This post presents some interresting tools for aeronautic studies.
Note: For several cases, I provide the binaries and documentation files. The main objective is not to spoil work issued by other people but to maitain the tools available even if the original website disappear. This is espacially true for &amp;ldquo;old&amp;rdquo; and non updated software.
If you&amp;rsquo;are the original author and don&amp;rsquo;t appreciate this pratice, please contact me.
Propeller PROP_DESIGN website: https://propdesign.</description></item><item><title>Free Software for Aeronautics</title><link>https://nagodede.github.io/posts/free-software-for-aeronautics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 18:08:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nagodede.github.io/posts/free-software-for-aeronautics/</guid><description>This post presents some interresting tools for aeronautic studies.
Propeller PROP_DESIGN website: https://propdesign.jimdofree.com/
PROP_DESIGN is open source, public domain, aircraft propeller design software. Although intended for traditional aircraft propellers, PROP_DESIGN supports:
Axial Flow Fans Counter-rotating Propellers Electric Ducted Fans - EDFs Geared Turbofans - GTFs Open Rotors Propfans Turbofans (both Rotors and Stators) Ultra-High Bypass Engines - UHBs Unducted Fans - UDFs CCBlade website: https://github.com/byuflowlab/CCBlade.jl
CCBlade is a Julia software using the blade element momentum method for propellers and turbines.</description></item></channel></rss>